Guide to the Haldun Hadimioglu Papers RG.043
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Haldun Hadimioglu Papers
1989-2013
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Hadimioglu, Haldun
RG.043
2 Linear Feet in 6 boxes
Box 1
Box 2
Box 3
Box 4
Box 5
Box 6
Biographical / Historical
Haldun Hadimioglu is currently an industry professor in the Department of Computer Science and Engineering at NYU Tandon. He began teaching in the Poly Computer Science department in 1985 and completed his Ph.D. in Computer Science at Poly in 1991.
Scope and Contents
Material covers records of Computer Science department meetings, faculty meetings, and specific committee meetings. Some meetings only have circulated agendas while others have related handouts and Haldun's handwritten notes.
Arrangement
Original order was maintained at the series and document level. Some folders are therefore chronologically non-consecutive.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open for research without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials were received from Professor Haldun Hadimioglu on May 29, 2019.
Minutes; Hadimioglu, Haldun
- Series I: Undergraduate Curriculum Standards Committee Meeting Materials, 2009-2013
  - UGCSC Meeting - 2/25/2013, February 25, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 2/4/2013, February 4, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 12/12/2012, December 12, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 11/26/2012, November 26, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 10/17/2012, October 17, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 9/25/2012, September 25, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 4/26/2012, April 26, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - HuSS 3-Credit Curriculum Proposal, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 1/17/2012, January 17, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 11/23/2011, November 23, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 10/26/2011, October 26, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 10/17/2011, October 17, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 3/30/2011, March 30, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 10/20/2010, October 20, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 11/10/2010, November 10, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 4/21/2010, April 21, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 4/14/2010, April 14, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 2/24/2010, February 24, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 1/20/2010, January 20, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 10/19/2009, October 19, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 4/27/2009, April 27, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 4/20/2009, April 20, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 4/13/2009, April 13, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 2/11/2009, February 11, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - UGCSC Faculty Meeting Materials, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Series II: Faculty Meeting Materials, 2008-2012
  - Faculty Meeting - 12/5/2012, December 5, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Meeting - 11/7/2012, November 7, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Meeting - 10/3/2012, October 3, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Meeting - 9/12/2012, September 12, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Meeting - 5/2/2012, May 2, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Meeting - 4/4/2012, April 4, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Meeting - 2/1/2012, February 1, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Meeting - 11/2/2011, November 2, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Meeting - 12/7/2011, December 7, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Meeting - 10/5/2011, October 5, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Meeting - 5/4/2011, May 4, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Faculty Meeting - 3/2/2011, March 2, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Faculty Meeting - 2/2/2011, February 2, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Faculty Meeting - 12/1/2010, December 1, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Faculty Meeting - 11/3/2010, November 3, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Meeting - 10/6/2010, October 6, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Faculty Meeting - 9/15/2010, September 15, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Faculty Meeting - 4/7/2010, April 7, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Meeting - 2/3/2010, February 3, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Faculty Meeting - 12/2/2009, December 2, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Faculty Meeting - 10/7/2009, October 7, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Faculty Meeting - 4/29/2009, April 29, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Faculty Meeting - 4/8/2009, April 8, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Faculty Meeting - 3/4/2009, March 4, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Faculty Meeting - 2/4/2009, February 4, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Faculty Meeting - 12/3/2008, December 3, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Faculty Meeting - 10/1/2008, October 1, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Faculty Meeting - 9/10/2008, September 10, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Faculty Meeting - 5/14/2008, May 14, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Faculty Meeting - 4/30/2008, April 30, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Faculty Meeting - 4/2/2008, April 2, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Faculty Meeting - 3/5/2008, March 5, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Series III: Computer Science Department Meeting Materials, 1992-2013
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 12/4/2013, December 4, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 7/11/2013, July 11, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 3/7/2013, March 7, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 1/31/2013, January 31, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 12/10/2012, December 10, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - CSE Departmental Retreat - 5/29/2012, May 29, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 5/2/2012, May 2, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 2/16/2012, February 16, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 2/2/2012, February 2, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 9/14/2011, September 14, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 4/7/2011, April 7, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 2/9/2011, February 9, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 12/22/2010, December 22, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 2/16/2010, February 16, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 11/30/2009, November 30, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 9/23/2009, September 23, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 5/6/2009, May 6, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 2/25/2009, February 25, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - CS Departmental Meeting - 9/29/2008, September 29, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - CS Departmental Meeting - 5/15/2008, May 15, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - CS Departmental Meeting - 9/26/2007, September 26, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 5/10/2007, May 10, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 2/14/2007, February 14, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 9/20/2006, September 20, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 5/17/2006, May 17, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 2/2/2006, February 2, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 9/21/2005, September 21, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 12/16/2004, December 16, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 6/30/2005, June 30, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 5/16/2005, May 16, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 4/20/2005, April 20, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 2/9/2005, February 9, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 10/27/2004, October 27, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 9/23/2004, September 23, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 4/20/2004, April 20, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 3/18/2004, March 18, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 2/11/2004, February 11, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - UGCSC Meeting - 1/26/2004, January 26, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 11/19/2003, November 19, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 10/29/2003, October 29, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 9/17/2003, September 17, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 12/11/2002, December 11, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 4/24/2002, April 24, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 2/13/2002, February 13, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 10/24/2001, October 24, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 10/18/2000, October 18, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 2/12/2001, February 12, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 5/25/2000, May 25, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 2/16/2000, February 16, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 9/29/1999, September 29,1999 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 4/7/1999, April 7, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 2/10/1999, February 10, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 5/25/1999, May 25, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Memorandum on CIS Cheating Policy - 8/18/1998, August 18, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 7/8/1998, July 8, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 4/1998, April 1998 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - CIS Departmental Meeting - 7/25/1997, July 25, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - CS Departmental Meeting - 2/10/1993, February 10, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - CS Departmental Meeting - 11/4/1992, November 4, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - CS TA Training - 9/1/1992, September 1, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Computer Science Departmental Proposals, 1992-2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Series IV: Computer Science Graduate Curriculum Materials, 1989-2007
  - Unit to Credit Change, April 2006 - March 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Qualifying Exams Counter-Proposal, December 1, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Changes to B.S./M.S. Program, February 2005 - September 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Changes to M.S. Program, April 1992 - February 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Course-Related Documents, June 1989, December 1991, May 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - PhD Student Minor Requirement Email, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Series V: Computer Science Curriculum Materials, 1992-2008
  - CSE Departmental Meeting - 11/24/2008, November 24, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - New B.S. Program in Computer Science (2000), September 1999, April 2000, May 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - New B.S. Program in Computer Science (1995), 1993, February 1995 - July 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - CS Architecture Courses, February 1994 - February 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - B.S. in Computer Science work (1993), July 1993 - December 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - B.S. in Computer Science work (1993), January 1993 - June 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - B.S. in Computer Science work (before 1993), 1986 - 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Course-Related Documents, February 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ABET - Computer Engineering (2004), June 2004, September 2004; 2004-09-13 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - ABET - Computer Science (2003), October 2001, November 2001, April 2002, May 2002, May 2003, October 2003 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ABET Criteria 2000 Materials, 1999, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ABET - Computer Engineering (1996), May 1995, September 1995, January 1996 - March 1996, November 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ABET - Computer Engineering (1990), May 1990, September 1990, October 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ABET Produced Documents, 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 6/9/2004, June 9, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 3/17/2003, March 17, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 10/15/2002, October 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 9/23/2002, September 23, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 4/23/2002, April 23, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 2/12/2002, February 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 3/8/2001, March 8, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Computer Science Course Proposals, March 2000 - April 2000 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mathematics Course Proposals, March 2000 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 12/21/1999, December 21, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Materials on Changes to CS 336R and CS 4, November 1999 - December 1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Computer Engineering Curriculum Development, June 1999, September 1999 - December 1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Materials on Computer Language Discussions, February 1996, September 1999 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Freshman Electrical and Computer Engineering Orientation Meeting - 9/3/1997, September 3, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 2/12/1997, February 12, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 11/27/1996, November 27, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Computer Engineering Steering Committee Meeting - 5/22/1995, May 22, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - EE and CompE - Change from 136 Credit to 128 Credit B.S., May 1995 - April 1996, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Other EE and CompE B.S. Degree Curricula, 1994, 1995, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - [Core Curriculum NON CS], February 1992 - May 1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Clean Slate Committee Work, November 1995 - November 1998 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Computer Science Enrollment and STEM Forums, 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Course Codes, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Authorization for Materials, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - High School Students Visiting Poly May 2002, 2002-05 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Series VI: Long Island Materials, 1993-1999
  - [Farmingdale Miscellaneous Documents], April 1995 - April 1999 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Internship Committee (Farming.), November 1993 - April 1994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Computer Facilities (Farmingdale), September 1993 - October 1993 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - OPEN HOUSE Farmingdale, October 1994, March 1997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Series VII: Miscellaneous Materials (by type), 1984-2002
  - University/Inter-Office Memoranda, July 1986 - May 2002, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Polytechnic Ten Year Plan Draft, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Executive Committee Progress Report and Position Paper, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Merit Scholar Article, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Polytechnic President's Report and Newsletter, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Sky Magazine Reprint, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - "The Changing Dynamics in Engineering Education at ASU" Article, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Draft of Enhancement of Teaching Quality and Memo, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Polytechnic Fulfilling The American Dream, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Polytechnic President's Report, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Polytechnic Cable Alumni Newsletter, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Call for Participation in Summer Workshops at Clemson University, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - UC Berkeley Pilot Teaching Project Documents, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - National Science Foundation Workshop Announcement, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Student Email Thread, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Stuart A. Steele CV, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Communications Project Email, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - MIT Summer Short Course Application, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - "Preparing for Promotion and Tenure" Article, circa 1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - MetroTech Fact Sheet, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Series VIII: Computer Boards, undated
  - Computer Board 1, 10" x 9", undated (Box 4)
  - Computer Board 2, 11" x 10", undated (Box 4)
  - Computer Board 3, 13" x 9", undated (Box 4)
  - Computer Board 4, 14" x 12", undated (Box 4)
  - Computer Board 5, 13" x 11", undated (Box 4)
  - Computer Board 6, 14" x 10", undated (Box 4)
  - Computer Board 7, 14" x 9.5", undated (Box 4)
  - Computer Board 8, 14" x 12", undated (Box 5)
  - Computer Board 9, 16" x 14", undated
  - Computer Board 10, 13" x 4", undated (Box 5)
  - Keyboard, 11" x 4", undated (Box 5)
- Series IX: Network Processor Design Books, 2003-2005
  - Network Processor Design: Issues and Practices Volume 1, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Network Processor Design: Issues and Practices Volume 1, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Network Processor Design: Issues and Practices Volume 2, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Network Processor Design: Issues and Practices Volume 2, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Network Processor Design: Issues and Practices Volume 2, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Network Processor Design: Issues and Practices Volume 2, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Network Processor Design: Issues and Practices Volume 3, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Network Processor Design: Issues and Practices Volume 3, 2005 (Box 3)